Jaideep Verma

North Alderwood Street Winter Springs, FL 32708

Phone: +18478747757

E-Mail: jaideepverma121@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Accomplished and energetic with a solid history of achievement in Kronos workforce and ADP etime specialist. Motivated leader with strong organizational and prioritization abilities. Areas of expertise include ADP payroll, Peoplesoft HCM and Kronos WFC

Skills

ADP Payroll Etime Time Management Administration and Management Critical Thinking Training and development Audio-Visual and Multimedia Collections Specialist Ms office Speaking

Experience

January 2014 to Present fortetime solutions, LLC New York, NY Kronos workforce & ADP etime implementaion consultant

Independent SR. Kronos Consultant ,with over 20 years experience of ADP etime & Kronos workforce experience.

Implemented with ADP etime & Kronos workforce suite for over 200 clients as 100k employees. Industries Included: Banking, Education, Healthcare, Hospitality, manufacturing.

Mentored a group of 150+ consultants, helping with training, best practices and shadowing phases of a client implementation.

Has Performed payroll functions, such as maintaining timekeeping information and processing and submitting payroll.

March 2004 to December 2013

ADP Florham Park Florham Park, NJ

Senior implemention Kronos and Etime consultant

Provide technical support and assistance in sales of ADP etime products.

Designed technical solutions to problems identified and negotiating solutions.

Use computers for various applications, such as database management or word processing.

Supervise other clerical staff and provide training and orientation to new staff.

January 2002 to February 2004 ASM Technologies Limited Bengaluru, KA Peoplesoft Functional Consulatant

Worked on upgrade products of GL,AP ,PR,ePRO,and EX modules. January 1997 to January 2002

Max Bupa Health Insurance Bangalore Bengaluru, KA

Claims officer - Manual testing And UAT

Manual Testing and UAT operations.

Education

April 1996 Penn State University State College, PA BTECH TECHNOLOGY Graduated with honors.